So this is the exciting part.
I wanted it to add an image from myself.
So that's also doable over here.
But how?
Clicking on this very image icon, right?
So if I click on this, as you see,
it says image reference, reference,
the visual styles, yep.
So I click on it.
And I will be able to upload an image.
In order to add an image reference to my prompt,
and in order to be able to include my own images,
like, for example, the logo of my brand, right?
I can add them as well over here.
So I click on upload an image.
And I go to the take of college branding.
And this one, I click on open.
And wait a little bit until my images uploaded.
So as you see, my images added over here.
And then I'll be able to add my prompt over here.